bloggingexperiment.com 2012-12-20

# Privacy Policy

_Last updated April 2, 2011_

BloggingExperiment.com (“BLOGEX”) has established this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

 **WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS  
**

This privacy policy covers BloggingExperiment.com’s treatment of personally identifiable information collected by BLOGEX through a website owned and operated by BLOGEX.

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that BLOGEX does not own or control, or of persons that BLOGEX does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which the BloggingExperiment.com website may link.

 **COLLECTION & USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
**

You can visit the websites of BLOGEX without revealing any personal information. However, BLOGEX needs certain personal information if you wish to purchase certain products, receive the BloggingExperiment.com newsletter, or use certain BLOGEX services.

Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. BLOGEX will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, and to contact you regarding new products and services.

By accessing the services of BLOGEX and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

 **COLLECTION & USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION  
**

BLOGEX automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. BLOGEX may use this information to customize the content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, BLOGEX does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.

 **INFORMATION SHARING & DISCLOSURE  
**

BLOGEX may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of BLOGEX to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information.

 **BLOGEX** **MAY OTHERWISE DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WHEN:**

(a) We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose.

(b) We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process.

(c) We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of BLOGEX.

(d) We find that your actions on our websites violate the BLOGEX Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

 **CONSENT**

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to BLOGEX. If you have provided personal information to BLOGEX and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please [notify us](http://bloggingexperiment.com/contact "Notify Us").

 **SECURITY**

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your BLOGEX Information is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, BLOGEX may use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.

Further, BLOGEX retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above or as required by law.

 **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
**

BLOGEX may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. When it does, BLOGEX will also revise the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of the BloggingExperiment.com website after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

 **QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS**

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please [contact us directly](http://bloggingexperiment.com/contact "Contact Us Directly").
